Guide to the Ida Merriam papers, 1926-1983 MS2086
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Reports and studies, 1934-1979; MS2086 Series 3
  - Social Service Research Policies, 1945-1971 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Social Security Reading List, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Social Security Programs in the United States, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Social Security Programs in the United States, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - State Differences in Income Distribution: Figures based on study of consumer purchases, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Statement by Joseph A Califano, Jr. Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1979 February 15 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - State Statistical Analysis Relating to Unemployment Compensation Simplification, 1939 January (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Statistics of Family Composition in Selected Areas of the United States Vol. 2, 1934-1936 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Reports and studies, undated (Box 54)
  - Statistics of Family Composition in Selected Areas of the United States Vol. 10, 1934-1942 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Statistical Materials on the Distribution of Federal Expenditures Among the States, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Study of the Problems of Medical Care for the Indingent [1/2], 1954 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Study of the Problems of Medical Care for the Indingent [2/2], 1954 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Survey of Social Security Statistics, 1944 March (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Summarized Proceedings - Conference of Labor Research Group, 1946 December 10 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Summary - Social Security and the Changing Roles of Men and Women, 1940 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Supplemental Security Income Program, 1973-1975 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Survey of Accident and Health Insurance, Bulletins No. 1, 2, and 3, 1945 November (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Survey of Accident and Health Insurance, Bulletins No. 4, 5, and 6, 1946 August (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - A system of Demographic, Manpower and Social Statistics series, Classifications and Social Indictors, 1971 April (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Tabular Summary of Statistics of Public Assistance, 1937 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Reports and studies, undated (Box 55)
  - Temporary Disability Insurance Coordinated with Unemployment Insurance, 1947 January (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Three Standards of Living for an Urban Family of four Persons, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Tips in Relation to Wages Under the Social Security Program, 1938 February (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Towards a Comprehensive Health Policy for the 1970's-A White Paper, 1971 May (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Trends in Public Assistance 1933-1939, 1940 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Unemployment Compensation rights of workers employed in more than one state, 1941 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Unemployment and Health Insurance in Great Britain 1911-1937, 1938 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Unemployment Compensation-What and Why? Social Security Board, 1937 March (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - United Nations Report on the World Social Situation, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - United Nations Report on the World Social Situation, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - United Nations Report on the World Social Situation, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - United Nations Economic and Social Council-Report of the First Session; Expert Group on a System of Demographic, Manpower and Social Statistics, 1970 August (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - United Nations Report on the World Social Situation, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Women and Social Security, 1972-1973 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Reports and studies, undated (Box 56)
  - Workers and Dependents in Urban Families, 1947 June (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Wage and Seperation Reporting in Unemployment Compensation, 1938 December (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Welfare Report (Incomplete), 1955 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Workmen's Compensation Benefit Payments-Estimate of Workmen's Compenstaion Payments, 1939 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Women and Social Security: Five Case Studies, 1972 June (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Work Plan Office of Research and Statistics, 1972-1973 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Women Under Social Security, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Women's Compensation Experience-Its Value for Administrative and Research Purposes in the Social Security Board, 1936 August (Box 56, Folder 8)